BRANDON MINGLEDORFF

16 Tanger Lake Cove · Jackson, TN 38305 brandonming@gmail.com · 731-394-2056 · brandonmingledorff.com

I am an engineer with extensive experience in software and web development - both front and back-end. I have a passion for learning and improving upon my skills. In my free time, I enjoy watching basketball and creating art.

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2018 – DECEMBER 2021

B.S. COMPUTER ENGINEERING, THE UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE KNOXVILLE

- GPA: 3.97
- Honors Leadership Program (2018 2020)

EXPERIENCE

JUNE 2021 - PRESENT

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN, HCA HEALTHCARE

Was the lead developer on several time and resource-saving business applications that are now used regularly by the Corporate Internal Audit Department and/or the entire HCA enterprise.

JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

TEACHING ASSISTANT, THE UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE KNOXVILLE

Taught C++, MIPS assembly, and computer architecture to undergraduate students at the University of Tennessee.

MAY 2019 - JULY 2020

LOT ASSOCIATE, THE HOME DEPOT

Was responsible for tasks that greatly improved my organizational skills such as maintaining the inside and outside of the store, taking customer phone calls, managing transactions and returns, and handling complaints.

SKILLS

- Programming (C, C++, Python, VHDL)
- Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, PHP)
- Graphic Design

- Data Science
- Organizational Skills (Communication, Time Management, Teamwork)
- Full-Stack Development

HONORS / AWARDS

•	Charles and Martha Sprankle Merit Scholarship	2020 - 2021
•	David and Joan Patterson Merit Scholarship	2020 - 2021
•	Dev Catalyst Coding Champion – Programming	2018
•	Dev Catalyst Coding Champion – Web Design	2017